Tours & Attractions; Adler Planetarium; Description to come.; 1300 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 922-7827	
Tours & Attractions; Amazing Chicago's Funhouse Maze; Squeezing, stomping, spinning... double over laughing... delightfully dizzy, twisting and turning -can you find your way out? It’s an exhilarating sensory experience for the whole family. Navigate your way through 4000 square feet of exhilarating sensory experiences. Lose yourself in the Mirror Maze, stumble your way through the Spinning ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (630) 990-4570	
Tours & Attractions; Anita Dee Yacht Charters; Anita Dee Yacht Charters has two luxurious vessels with alternate docking locations and flexible charter times. Private group charters available for up to 345 guests.; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 379-3191	
Tours & Attractions; Buckingham Fountain; This popular historic landmark and tourist attraction offers visitors a dazzling music, light and water show, which runs dusk-11pm, spring through the end of fall. The fountain table can also be rented for large special events.; Columbus Drive and Congress Parkway Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 742-4847	
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Children's Museum; Want world-class fun? Splash, climb, build, learn and explore at the award-winning Chicago Children’s Museum, located at Navy Pier! It’s three floors of fun for children and families. Climb on a ship, hide in a treehouse, construct a building, dam up a river, drive a fire truck, tinker with ... ; 700 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 527-1000	
Tours & Attractions; Chicago History Museum; Come explore Chicago! Groups of ten or more receive discounted rates for museum tours or our unique walking and boat tours. Step on guides and delicious lunch options. Hear the stories, see the legends, dispel the myths with our trained guides.; 1601 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 642-4600	
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Loop Bridges; ChicagoLoopBridges -- Walking tours along the Chicago River provide the opportunity to enjoy Chicago's largest kinetic sculptures in their natural habitat. Chicago's magnificent downtown movable bridges are a vital part of Chicago's story. Whether you are a visitor or a native, take the opportunity to see these icons of ... ; 155 N. Harbor Dr. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 540-0696	
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Trolley and Double Decker Co.; Ride The Red and Green Trolleys(R). Ride Chicago's Big Red Double Deckers(tm).The Chicago Trolley & Double Decker Co. has been voted Chicago’s Best Tour and is the city’s largest sightseeing company. This is the essential overview tour for all Chicago vacation packages. Entertaining tour guides tell stories of history, ... ; Water Tower Pumping Station Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (773) 648-5000	
Tours & Attractions; Chicago's First Lady Cruises; Welcome aboard Chicago's finest fleet! Choose Chicago's First Lady and the Chicago Architecture Foundation to experience 90-minutes of amazing! The Official Chicago Architecture Foundation River Cruise departs only from the Chicago Riverwalk, just 3-blocks North of Millennium Park at the Southeast corner of the Michigan Ave Bridge at Wacker ... ; 112 E. Wacker Dr. on Chicago's Riverwalk Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (800) 982-2787	
Tours & Attractions; Daley Civic Center; Picasso Sculpture, "Under the Picasso"; 50 W. Washington St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 603-7980	
Tours & Attractions; Eli's Cheesecake World; Visit Eli’s Cheesecake World, a bakery, café and retail store on Chicago’s northwest side, where you can enjoy Eli’s Tasting and Traditions Experience daily at 1pm including a free slice of Eli’s Cheesecake. Group tour packages are also available. Eli’s Cheesecake annual events include Eli’s at Taste of Chicago, ... ; 6701 W. Forest Preserve Dr. Chicago, IL 60634; Chicago; (773) 736-3417	
Tours & Attractions; Frank Lloyd Wright's Robie House; Frank Lloyd Wright's Robie House sparked a revolution in residential architecture whose influence still reverberates today. Designated by the American Institute of Architects as one of the 10 most significant structures of the 20th century, this American treasure is celebrated as one of Chicago's most important works of art. ... ; 5757 S. Woodlawn Ave. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (312) 994-4000	
Tours & Attractions; Garfield Park Conservatory; One of the largest gardens under glass in the nation. This conservatory features five permanent collections, an indoor children's garden, outdoor gardens and five annual flower shows. Open daily 9am-5pm. Admission and parking are free.; 300 N. Central Park Ave. Chicago, IL 60624; Chicago; (312) 746-5100	
Tours & Attractions; Grant Park Rose Gardens; Lush gardens filled with roses, just steps away from Buckingham Fountain.; Columbus Dr. & Congress Pkwy. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 742-4838	
Tours & Attractions; Hershey's Chicago; Experience our unique, interactive retail store and bakery located on Chicago's Magnificent Mile. Operate Hershey's Magnificent Chocolate Works Machine to become a factory worker, with a photo ID and your own assortment of chocolates! Customize a Hershey bar wrapper with a photo (take one in the store or bring ... ; 822 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 337-7711	
Tours & Attractions; John Hancock Observatory; Leisure Visitors & Meeting Professionals: At 1,000ft, John Hancock Observatory offers a unique setting for everything from small gatherings to large groups up to 695, unique cocktail parties to sit down dinners; your clients will not be disappointed. Affordable food and beverage packages have been specifically designed to wow ... ; 875 N. Michigan Ave., 94th Floor Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 751-3681	
Tours & Attractions; Lincoln Park Conservatory; Peaceful and enchanting gardens in the heart of Lincoln Park, adjacent to the zoo. Open 9am-5pm daily. Free admission.; 2391 N. Stockton Dr. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 742-7736	
Tours & Attractions; Lincoln Park Zoo; See roaring lions, playful meerkats and majestic gorillas just minutes from downtown Chicago. Lincoln Park Zoo is free, open and amazing every day of the year. Visitors can go nose-to-nose with gorillas and chimpanzees, howl with red wolves, peer into a black bear den and immerse themselves in the ... ; Cannon Drive at Fullerton Parkway Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 742-2000	
Tours & Attractions; Lucky Strike Lanes; Lucky Strike offers Classic American fare with a twist. 18 lanes and 11 billiards tables along with elegant lounge space perfect for your next event!; 322 E. Illinois St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 245-8331	
Tours & Attractions; Macy's on State Street; Macy's on State Street (formerly Marshall Field Company flagship store) has been a Chicago destination for more than a century. As the second largest department store in the world, Macy's flagship features 10 floors of retail space, an unparalleled merchandise selection, five unique restaurants and architectural icons including the ... ; 111 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 781-1000	
Tours & Attractions; Millennium Park; Millennium Park is an award-winning center for art, music, architecture and landscape design. It's prominent features are the Frank Gehry-designed Jay Pritzker Pavilion, the most sophisticated outdoor concert venue of its kind in the United States; the interactive Crown Fountain by Jaume Plensa; the contemporary Lurie Garden designed by ... ; 201 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 744-6050	
Tours & Attractions; Museum of Science and Industry; Specializing in Leisure, Incentive and Student groups….Choose custom tour itineraries in: Art, Architecture, Food, Fashion, Ethnic Neighborhoods, Music, and Theater…or mix it up! We go behind the scenes to the real Chicago with exclusive access to the city’s hidden gems! Enjoy a Cruise on Chicago’s Lakefront, a Progressive Ethnic ... ; 57th Street and Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 684-1414	
Tours & Attractions; Navy Pier; Presenting Hollywood's biggest blockbuster films in IMAX 3D on our soaring 6 story tall screen. Located in the Family Pavilion at the entrance to historic Navy Pier.  Reserve your specific seat at www.imax.com/chicago. Group rates for 10-400, call 312-595-5987. Hours: Mon.- Sun. 10:00am-10:00pm; 600 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 595-5300	
Tours & Attractions; Navy Pier IMAX Theatre; Cynthia Noble Private Art Tours & Events offers custom art tours of public art, the Art Institute of Chicago, the Museum of Contemporary Art and neighborhood gallery walks for individuals, families and social or corporate groups.; 700 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 595-5629	
Tours & Attractions; Segway Experience of Chicago; Join Shoreline for a dramatic Architecture River Tour, exciting Lake Michigan Skyline Tour , Walking Tour or thrilling Fireworks Cruise! Architecture Tours now depart from both Gateway Park at Navy Pier or the northeast corner of the Michigan Avenue Bridge and are led by experienced, entertaining Shoreline guides. Learn ... ; 224 S. Michigan Ave., Ste. 113 Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 663-0600	
Tours & Attractions; Skydeck Chicago; The South Shore Cultural Center with castle-like interior and grandiose ballrooms, ornate chandeliers and ample meeting space includes a 65-acre park and surrounding grounds, a golf course, nature sanctuary, bathing beach and an impressive multiuse facility, which originated as the South Shore Country Club.; 233 S. Wacker Dr. Chicago, IL 60606; Chicago; (312) 875-9696	
Tours & Attractions; Spirit of Chicago; 3 unforgettable food adventures and chocolate and dessert tours too! Savor the Sweet Flavors of Chicago. Join Tastebud in the city of deep dish pizza, Chicago-style hot dogs and Italian beef. Enjoy tastes of these iconic dishes synonymous with our great city and be introduced to other foods that ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (866) 835-7245	
Tours & Attractions; Wateriders Kayak Tours & Rentals Riverwalk; Historic House & Mansion Tours are offered 2 days per week for guests and other visitors including food and drinks. Some tours include music package tours where live music performances include: Blues, Jazz, Rock and Pop Music.; 950 N. Kingsbury St./600 W. Chicago Ave. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 953-9287	
Tours & Attractions; WhirlyBall Chicago; Walk with us along Chicago’s streets–and her alleys, bridges, cemeteries, parks, and rivers–to learn the stories of how Chicago became today’s great city. Because, like Rome, the Windy City wasn’t built in a day! On a WOW Tour, you’re going to get a history lesson. But history like you’ve ... ; 1880 W. Fullerton Ave. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 486-7777	
Museums; Art Institute of Chicago; Traveling to Chicago? No trip is complete without a visit to the city’s #1 museum, also voted #1 Chicago attraction by TripAdvisor—out of 300 venues! Explore America’s greatest collection of Impressionist paintings, including world-famous works by Monet, Renoir, Seurat, and Van Gogh. Then discover the critically acclaimed Modern Wing, ... ; 111 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 443-3600	
Museums; Chicago Children's Museum; Want world-class fun? Splash, climb, build, learn and explore at the award-winning Chicago Children’s Museum, located at Navy Pier! It’s three floors of fun for children and families. Climb on a ship, hide in a treehouse, construct a building, dam up a river, drive a fire truck, tinker with ... ; 700 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 527-1000	
Museums; Chicago History Museum; The Chicago History Museum offers exhibitions and public programs that illuminate the city's past, engage the city's present, and point to Chicago's future. Vivian Maier's Chicago explores the city through the eyes of the nanny turned photographer who wowed the world with breathtaking images of everyday urban America. Maier's ... ; 1601 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 642-4600	
Museums; City Gallery at the Historic Water Tower; Located in one of Chicago's most popular landmarks, the new City Gallery features photographs of Chicago by Chicago photographers.; 806 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 742-0808	
Museums; Driehaus Museum; Steps away from Chicago’s Michigan Avenue, the Richard H. Driehaus Museum offers visitors a fascinating view of one of the few remaining examples of the palatial homes erected by the wealthy of America’s Gilded Age. The galleries, elegantly furnished with period pieces selected from the Driehaus Collection, are presented ... ; 40 E. Erie Street Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 482-8933	
Museums; Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago; Visit the Money Museum at the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago. View rare currency and displays of millions of dollars. Detect counterfeit currency and create your own unique dollar bill featuring your portrait. All visitors receive souvenir shredded money. Open Monday thru Friday: 8:30am to 5:00pm. Adult visitors must ... ; 230 S. LaSalle St. Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 322-2400	
Museums; The Field Museum; Leisure Visitors: Discover Sue, the world's largest and most complete T. rex ever found! Descend into an Egyptian tomb and see 23 Egyptian mummies and 5,000 year-old hieroglyphics, shrink to 1/100th of your natural size and get a bug's-eye view in Underground Adventure, come nose-to-nose with the man-eating lions ... ; 1400 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 922-9410	
Museums; Museum of Broadcast Communications; Mission of MBC: To collect, preserve and present historic and contemporary radio and television content as well as educate, inform & entertain the public through its archives, public programs, screenings, exhibits, publications & online access to its resources.; 360 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60654-5411; Chicago; (312) 245-8200	
Museums; Museum of Contemporary Art; One of Chicago's most sophisticated sites. Guests can sip champagne while strolling through the sculpture garden and terrace overlooking Lake Michigan or listen to music while viewing some of the world's most celebrated art. Take a free, guided tour, stroll through our grand, barrel-vaulted galleries overlooking Lake Michigan and ... ; 220 E. Chicago Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 280-2660	
Museums; Museum of Science and Industry; The Museum of Science and Industry is the largest science museum in the Western Hemisphere! Housed in the only remaining building from the 1893 World’s Fair, MSI is a Chicago must-see! You’ll experience 14 acres of hands-on exhibits and have the chance to stand before a 40-foot tornado; climb ... ; 57th Street and Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 684-1414	
Museums; Shedd Aquarium; At Shedd Aquarium, animals connect you to the living world, inspiring you to make a difference. From whales to snails, tarantulas to turtles, you’ll meet 32,500 creatures from aquatic habitats around the world. Explore Shedd’s Abbott Oceanarium, where you can get face to face with beluga whales, dolphins, sea ... ; 1200 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 939-2438	
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Blue Man Group; Blue Man Group is a wildly popular entertainment phenomenon currently in an open-ended run. The production provides its audience with a unique and thrilling multi-sensory experience that fuses innovative theatrical spectacle and powerful original music with hilarious comedy, art, vaudeville and science to create a performance experience unlike any ... ; 3133 N. Halsted St. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 348-4000
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Broadway In Chicago; Broadway In Chicago brings Broadway's biggest shows to Chicago's finest theaters. On the stages of the Oriental Theatre, Cadillac Palace Theatre, Bank of America Theatre, Broadway Playhouse and the Auditorium Theatre of Roosevelt University see shows direct from Broadway and world premieres destined for Broadway. Current/Upcoming offerings include: THE ... ; 17 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 977-1701
Theaters &	Performing Arts; ComedySportz Theatre; Now in our 26th season, ComedySportz is a unique blend of fast and funny improv comedy that is appropriate for all ages. Two teams of improvisers play short-form improv games in front of a referee and the audience votes for the team that makes them laugh harder. You, the ... ; 929 W. Belmont Ave. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 549-8080
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Goodman Theatre; Goodman Theatre, Chicago’s oldest and largest not-for-profit theater, has won international renown for the quality of productions, the depth and diversity of artistic leadership, and the excellence of its many community and educational programs. The Goodman is committed to producing both classic and contemporary works, giving full voice to ... ; 170 N. Dearborn St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 443-3800
Theaters &	Performing Arts; The Joffrey Ballet; Chicago's premier ballet company.; Joffrey Tower, 10 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 739-0120
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Million Dollar Quartet; Chicago's smash hit musical inspired by the famed 1956 Sun Studios recording session that brought together legendary Rock N' Roll icons Johnny Cash, Jerry Lee Lewis, Carl Perkins and Elvis Presley. Hear the greatest hits from these music legends including "Blue Suede Shoes", "Great Balls of Fire" and more. ... ; Apollo Theater Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 935-6100
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Steppenwolf Theatre Company; Steppenwolf Theatre Company is America’s longest standing, most distinguished ensemble theater, producing nearly 700 performances and events annually in its three Chicago theater spaces—the 515-seat Downstairs Theatre, the 299-seat Upstairs Theatre and the 80-seat Garage Theatre. Formed in 1976 by a collective of actors, Steppenwolf has grown into an ... ; 1650 N. Halsted St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 335-1650
Shopping; 900 North Michigan Shops; Recognized as the lead anchor of Chicago's vibrant Magnificent Mile shopping district, 900 North Michigan Shops is a destination for style and sophistication unparalleled anywhere else in the Midwest. This architecturally stunning property features a 6-level Bloomingdale's and over 70 upscale shops that include a line-up of world-renowned brands ... ; 900 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 915-3916	
Shopping; American Girl Place; Discover why American Girl Place® Chicago is more than just a store—it’s a place for her imagination to soar! She’ll love exploring the worlds of her favorite characters filled with doll collections, books, outfits and more. From inspiring historical characters to the contemporary Girl of the Year® dolls, she's ... ; 835 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 943-9400	
Shopping; Bloomingdale's; The Chicago flagship store features six levels of upscale shopping including men's, women's and children's clothing, shoes and cosmetics. Spring 2013 will bring an expanded and completely revamped Women's Shoe department on the third floor featuring a new space and representing the latest in women's fashion. The store will ... ; 900 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 440-4596	
Shopping; Garrett Popcorn Shops; The Original, Handcrafted Gourmet Popcorn For more than 60 years, Garrett Popcorn Shops® has attracted passionate fans around the world with the enticing aroma and taste of their handcrafted, gourmet popcorn. Every batch of Garrett Popcorn is handmade throughout the day in old-fashioned copper kettles using secret family recipes ... ; 625 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 944-2630	
Shopping; Hershey's Chicago; Experience our unique, interactive retail store and bakery located on Chicago's Magnificent Mile.  Operate Hershey's Magnificent Chocolate Works Machine to become a factory worker, with a photo ID and your own assortment of chocolates! Customize a Hershey bar wrapper with a photo (take one in the store or bring ... ; 822 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 337-7711	
Shopping; Lillstreet Art Center; Visit Chicago’s largest visual arts center. Founded in 1975, Lillstreet Art Center is a large community of artists and students working side-by-side in a friendly environment, which encourages and inspires artistic growth in the individual. Our center on Ravenswood Ave., boasts state-of-art equipment and more than 800 art classes ... ; 4401 N. Ravenswood Ave. Chicago, IL 60640; Chicago; (773) 769-4226	
Shopping; Macy's; Our Magnificent Mile location offers eight floors of designer fashions, accessories, shoes, cosmetics and house wares. Extended holiday hours. 835 N. Michigan Ave., 312-335-7700, www.macys.com.; 835 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 335-7700	
Shopping; Macy's on State Street; Macy's on State Street (formerly Marshall Field Company flagship store) has been a Chicago destination for more than a century. As the second largest department store in the world, Macy's flagship features 10 floors of retail space, an unparalleled merchandise selection, five unique restaurants and architectural icons including the ... ; 111 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 781-1000	
Shopping; Mary Mary Gifts; Mary Mary is Chicago's most unique gift and home furnishings boutique, located just steps from the Magnificent Mile and tucked away in a 133 year old Brownstone. Whether you are shopping for men, women or children, you will always find the perfect gift at Mary Mary!; 706 N. Dearborn St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 654-8100	
Shopping; The Merchandise Mart; 200+ luxury showrooms for kitchen, bath & building products, custom home furnishings, fabrics, floor & wall coverings, lighting, antiques & more.; 222 Merchandise Mart Plz. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 527-4141	
Shopping; Nordstrom Michigan Avenue; Nordstrom, one of the nation's leading fashion specialty retailers, offers its Michigan Avenue customers 271,000 sq. ft., four levels of contemporary and classic shoes, clothing, and accessories for the entire family. A wide range of special services and amenities are available including personal stylists, concierge, in-store alterations, shoe shine ... ; 55 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 464-1515	
Shopping; Pastoral Artisan Cheese, Bread & Wine; Pastoral Artisan Cheese, Bread & Wine, is an award-winning European-inspired neighborhood cheese, specialty food and wine shop offering the highest quality, cut-to-order domestic and international specialty cheeses, freshly baked breads, perfectly chosen accompaniments and small production wines, along with hand-crafted, cheese loving beers. Over time we have become known ... ; 53 E. Lake St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (773) 472-4781	
Shopping; Saks Fifth Avenue Chicago; Known for its service- featuring the best fashion the world has to offer in women's, men's, and children's apparel, plus accessories. Personal shopping service available.; 700 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 944-6500	
Shopping; Water Tower Place; At the pinnacle of Chicago's famed Magnificent Mile, Water Tower Place is Chicago's premier shopping destination. Its stunning eight-level atrium features American Girl Place, Macy's, Broadway In Chicago's Broadway Playhouse and more than 100 of your favorite stores, spas and restaurants, plus a mix of distinctive specialty shops and ... ; 835 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 440-3166	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Blue Chicago; Blue Chicago is world-renowned offering the best of Chicago's blues musicians and vocalists performing in an intimate and friendly atmosphere. Conveniently located in the River North Entertainment district near the major hotels. Open 7 nights a week from 8 p.m. music beginning at 9 p.m.; 536 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 661-0100	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Buddy Guy's Legends; Chicago's premier blues club now at it's new location, owned by Buddy Guy; local and national blues bands every night. Enjoy a full menu and bar.; 700 S. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 427-1190	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; ComedySportz Theatre; Now in our 26th season, ComedySportz is a unique blend of fast and funny improv comedy that is appropriate for all ages. Two teams of improvisers play short-form improv games in front of a referee and the audience votes for the team that makes them laugh harder. You, the ... ; 929 W. Belmont Ave. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 549-8080	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Ditka's Restaurant; Chicago's own Johnny Vincent sings the sounds of Frank Sintara, Louie Armstrong, Johnny Cash, and many, many, more. Every Tuesday through Saturday with no cover charge.; 100 E. Chestnut St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 587-8989	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Howl at the Moon; Howl at the Moon is a live music venue providing dueling piano show entertainment 7 nights a week! It's a singing & dancing interactive form of entertainment where you name the songs you want to hear and we play them as you sing along!; 26 W. Hubbard St. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 863-7427	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Kerryman Bar and Restaurant; The Kerryman offers a sleek but warm vibe. Irish born and trained Executive Chef Damien Moloney creates an upscale menu that features comfort dishes.; 661 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 335-8121	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Lucky Strike Lanes; Specialty cocktails and classic American fare in the upscale bowling/billiards lounge and sports bar with 18 projection-screen and 22 plasma TVs.; 322 E. Illinois St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 245-8331	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Lyric Opera of Chicago; Lyric Opera of Chicago is one of the world's greatest opera companies. It is renowned internationally for its artistic excellence and breath-taking productions. Lyric's performances feature wonderful music and the greatest singers in the world performing without microphones! The 3,563 seat theatre is the second-largest opera auditorium in North ... ; 20 N. Wacker Dr., Ste. 860 Chicago, IL 60606; Chicago; (312) 332-2244	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; M Lounge; M Lounge is an intimate martini lounge that is warmly lit with candles, sconces and blue lighting which illuminates the vast selection of spirits. Honey and brown walls, burgundy velvet curtains, comfy sofas, table seating in hues of chocolates & sage, and a 28 ft walnut bar make this ... ; 1520 S. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 447-0201	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Million Dollar Quartet; Chicago's smash hit musical inspired by the famed 1956 Sun Studios recording session that brought together legendary Rock N' Roll icons Johnny Cash, Jerry Lee Lewis, Carl Perkins and Elvis Presley. Hear the greatest hits from these music legends including "Blue Suede Shoes", "Great Balls of Fire" and more. ... ; Apollo Theater Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 935-6100	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Second City; Celebrating over 50 years as the birthplace of Chicago-style improv and sketch comedy, The Second City has launched the careers of John Belushi, Mike Myers, Tina Fey, Bill Murray, Stephen Colbert, Steve Carell and many others. Schedule is as follows:Mon.-Thurs. 8pm; Fri. 8pm and 11pm; Sat. 8pm and 11pm; ... ; 1616 N. Wells St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 337-3992	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Sports Corner; Sports Corner is a three floor sports bar located across the street from Wrigley Field featuring outdoor roof deck and second floor al fresco dining.; 956 W. Addison St. Chicago, IL 60613; Chicago; (773) 929-1441	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Tavern at the Park; The Tavern Tree House is Chicago's hottest roof top deck. Spectacular views of Millennium Park and historical Michigan Avenue. Open year round with a glass enclosed atrium section. Come and enjoy your favorite game while relaxing in overstuffed couches or have a full dinner while taking in the view. ... ; 130 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 552-0070	
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; UP Comedy Club; What's UP? UP Comedy Club is Chicago's new premier comedy club. Featuring the best in headline stand-up comedy, sketch comedy and improv revues created and presented by Second City Theatricals, UP Comedy Club is Chicago's hot new destination for comedy with shows 7 nights a week! In addition to ... ; 230 W. N. Ave., 3rd Floor Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 662-4562	