Tours & Attractions; #1 Chicago Tours; At STEVE'S SEGWAY TOURS and TRIKKE CHICAGO, we provide you with the most educational, AND the most fun tour of Chicago! Our passionate and patient tour guides will instruct you on how to properly operate your own personal Segway or Trikke Carving Vehicle, making sure that you are comfortable ... ; 155 N. Harbor Dr Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 946-9467
Tours & Attractions; 63rd Street Beach House; Unique two-floor, open-air building overlooking Lake Michigan with quaint courtyards.; 6300 Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (312) 742-4847
Tours & Attractions; Absolutely Chicago Segway Tours; Leisure Visitors: If you’re looking for fun things to do in Chicago, try a guided Segway tour! Segways are easy to learn and exciting to ride! Absolutely Chicago Segway Tours gives you breathtaking views of Chicago’s famous attractions: Navy Pier, the Museum Campus, Lake Michigan, Buckingham Fountain, Millennium and ... ; Now at 2 locations (please call for more information) Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 552-5100
Tours & Attractions; Accenting Chicago Events & Tours; Accenting Chicago is in its 20th year as the city's premier tour operator offering a full range of day, multi-day & overnight itineraries for groups of all types including students, seniors, corporate & associations and special interest groups. In addition to our many favorite tours, we are pleased to ... ; 445 W. Erie St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 819-5363
Tours & Attractions; Adler Planetarium; Description to come.; 1300 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 922-7827
Tours & Attractions; All Trusted Tours and Attractions of Chicago; Welcome to the "Windy City", Chicago, Illinois! Founded in 1833 as an economically strategic location between the Great Lakes and the Mississippi, Chicago has grown to be one of the most important cities in the United States and the world. It is the third most populous city in the ... ; Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (800) 844-7601
Tours & Attractions; Amazing Chicago's Funhouse Maze; Squeezing, stomping, spinning... double over laughing... delightfully dizzy, twisting and turning -can you find your way out? It’s an exhilarating sensory experience for the whole family. Navigate your way through 4000 square feet of exhilarating sensory experiences. Lose yourself in the Mirror Maze, stumble your way through the Spinning ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (630) 990-4570
Tours & Attractions; Anita Dee Yacht Charters; Anita Dee Yacht Charters has two luxurious vessels with alternate docking locations and flexible charter times. Private group charters available for up to 345 guests.; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 379-3191
Tours & Attractions; Bike and Roll Chicago; Bike and Roll is celebrating 20 years of fun in Chicago. We offer bicycle rentals, guided bike tours, and Segway tours from 4 convenient locations; Millennium Park, Navy Pier, Riverwalk, and 53rd Street. Chicago’s lakefront trail boasts 18 miles of car free bike paths, and it is the best ... ; 239 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 729-1000
Tours & Attractions; Bobby's Bike Hike - Quality Tours, Rentals, & Urban Adventures; Bobby's Bike Hike offers award-winning, original tours of Chicago for a variety of interests, ages, and fitness levels. Choose between our original Lakefront Neighborhoods bicycle tour, City Lights at Night tour, Historic Hyde Park tour, Bobby's Tike Hike: Kid's Edition, or the Bikes, Bites, & Brews tour. Our experienced ... ; 465 N. McClurg Ct. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 915-0995
Tours & Attractions; Buckingham Fountain; This popular historic landmark and tourist attraction offers visitors a dazzling music, light and water show, which runs dusk-11pm, spring through the end of fall. The fountain table can also be rented for large special events.; Columbus Drive and Congress Parkway Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 742-4847
Tours & Attractions; Buckingham Fountain Pavilions; A distinctive, historical backdrop for your event in the heart of Chicago's Loop.; Columbus Dr. and Congress Parkway Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 742-4838
Tours & Attractions; Build-A-Bear Workshop; Located at Navy Pier, Build-A-Bear Workshop is a beary special interactive experience where you make your own furry friend. Call for store hours.; Navy Pier, 700 E. Grand Ave., Ste. GF12 Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 832-0114
Tours & Attractions; Cancer Survivor's Garden; Intimate, exclusive corridor of greenery and gorgeous plantings overlooking Grant Park.; 337 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 742-4847
Tours & Attractions; Centennial Fountain & Water Arc; May 1 - October 1; 10am-12 midnight.; 300 E. McClurg Ct. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 751-6633
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Architecture Foundation; The Chicago Architecture Foundation (CAF) offers over 85 exciting tours of Chicago including the #1 architecture tour in the city: the Chicago Architecture Foundation River Cruise aboard Chicago's First Lady Cruises. Our other tours include walking, bus, bike, and Segway tours. Space fills quickly, so book now at http://www.architecture.org ... ; 224 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 922-3432
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Beer Experience; See and learn about Chicago neighborhoods on our beer tours! We combine Chicago history with a variety of beer tastings, including local microbrews.; Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (312) 841-0456
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Children's Museum; Want world-class fun? Splash, climb, build, learn and explore at the award-winning Chicago Children’s Museum, located at Navy Pier! It’s three floors of fun for children and families. Climb on a ship, hide in a treehouse, construct a building, dam up a river, drive a fire truck, tinker with ... ; 700 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 527-1000
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Chinese Cultural Institute, Inc.; We know Chinatown better than anybody else! With over 12 years of experience giving tours in Chinatown area, we supply the most original Chinatown tours. Join our knowledgable tour guides for an insider's view of this unique cultural and food destination of over 100 year. Our Chinatown Food and ... ; 2131 S. Archer Ave., #104 Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 842-1988
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Chocolate Tours; Enjoy a guided walking and tasting tour of the finest local chocolate shops and cafes and sample scrumptious chocolate treats at each stop!; 500 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 929-2939
Tours & Attractions; Chicago CityPASS; Save 49% off Chicago’s best attractions, plus skip lines. Chicago CityPASS includes VIP admission to: Shedd Aquarium, The Field Museum, Skydeck Chicago, Adler Planetarium OR Art Institute of Chicago and Museum of Science and Industry OR John Hancock Observatory. Valid 9-days. Cost: Adult $89 (value $174); Child (3-11) $79. ... ; Purchase from participating attractions Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (208) 787-4300
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Detours; Smart, creative, and engaging guided tours of history, culture, and architecture for curious people. Explore stories and places even locals don't know with regularly scheduled tours for the public, and private group tours for student groups, corporate team-building, and convention groups. Founded by former Rick Steves tour guide Amanda ... ; Various Locations Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 350-1131
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Dine-Around; CHICAGO DINE-AROUND - PUBLIC TOURS: Embark on a unique adventure to Chicago's best restaurants. How it works: During the Progressive Dining Tour, guests travel around Chicago in a stylish coach bus to enjoy Hors D'oeuvres served at the first restaurant, the Main Course at a second restaurant, and Dessert ... ; Various Locations Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 437-3463
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Food Planet Food Tours; Chicago Food Planet Food Tours offer 3-hour food tasting & cultural walking tours that specialize in combining delicious food and drink tastings with some serious fun in Chicago’s most delicious, off-the-beaten-path neighborhoods. Rated the #1 Food Tour by TripAdvisor with over 1,000 reviews, CFP was recognized for their ongoing ... ; 830 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 445-9948
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Gray Line; Operator of tours for individuals and groups by coaches, trolleys and UpperDeckers. Custom-made tours for spouse programs. Deluxe charter buses for expo and conventions, shuttle bus services. All type of transfers provided including airports, rail terminals and attractions of museums and skydeck of John Hancock Tower.; Various Locations Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 251-3107
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Greeter; Completely free and uniquely customized to your own interests, Chicago Greeter is a year-round service that offers visitors the opportunity to explore Chicago with an insider leading the way. Local volunteers impart their love of Chicago to visitors on free guided walking tours highlighting Chicago’s many neighborhoods, history and ... ; 72 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 945-4231
Tours & Attractions; Chicago History Museum; Come explore Chicago! Groups of ten or more receive discounted rates for museum tours or our unique walking and boat tours. Step on guides and delicious lunch options. Hear the stories, see the legends, dispel the myths with our trained guides.; 1601 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 642-4600
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Line Cruises; Tour Chicago's world -renowned architecture aboard one of our 3 vessels traversing the Chicago River or experience Chicago's rich history on our Historical Lake or River Cruise. Cruises sail daily April through November. Group rates and private charters are available.; Ogden Slip Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 527-2002
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Loop Bridges; ChicagoLoopBridges -- Walking tours along the Chicago River provide the opportunity to enjoy Chicago's largest kinetic sculptures in their natural habitat. Chicago's magnificent downtown movable bridges are a vital part of Chicago's story. Whether you are a visitor or a native, take the opportunity to see these icons of ... ; 155 N. Harbor Dr. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 540-0696
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Music Tour; We provide guided bus tours & mini pub crawls of Chicago music history, including blues, rock, jazz & soul. Our expert guides carefully select playlists of songs that tell the stories of each site and stop. Our tours include: *Chicago Bound Blues Tour - Learn the story of Chicago ... ; 3617 N. Christiana Ave. Chicago, IL 60618; Chicago; (872) 228-5382
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Park District; Explore one of our more than 500 parks and playgrounds this summer! The Chicago Park District offers scenic views, historic buildings and miles of lakeshore to enjoy. Call for more information on park locations. Movies & Concerts series: Pack a picnic, grab a blanket and head out to your ... ; 541 N. Fairbanks Ct. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 742-7529
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Photo Safaris; If you love to take pictures and travel, or want your group to experience Chicago's icons and have beautiful photos as souvenirs then our photo safaris are for you! A professional photographer takes you or your group to photographic venues and around landmark Chicago destinations while giving you tips ... ; 55 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 470-6704
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Pizza Tours; Bus guided tour of culturally significant & neighborhood pizzerias. See Chicago One Slice At A Time as you taste the best neighborhood Chicago pizzas.; Various Locations Chicago, IL 60607; Chicago; (800) 979-3370
Tours & Attractions; The Chicago Tour Company; Let The Chicago Tour Company show you the best the Windy City has to offer. Looking for a step-on guide, a day-trip, a multi-day trip, or a tour escort? We are the best one-stop shop for a customized tour experience! We can create the perfect Chicago tour for you! ; 422 W. Melrose St. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 857-3345
Tours & Attractions; Chicago Trolley and Double Decker Co.; Ride The Red and Green Trolleys(R). Ride Chicago's Big Red Double Deckers(tm).The Chicago Trolley & Double Decker Co. has been voted Chicago’s Best Tour and is the city’s largest sightseeing company. This is the essential overview tour for all Chicago vacation packages. Entertaining tour guides tell stories of history, ... ; Water Tower Pumping Station Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (773) 648-5000
Tours & Attractions; Chicago's Finest Tours, Inc.; We are Chicago’s most dynamic and fun entertainment alternative! We offer our guests highly passionate and energy-packed activities ranging from walking tours, bus tours and highly advanced scavenger hunts – Ultimate Quest. We distinguish ourselves by providing our guests captivating storytelling, keen visualizations and infectious enthusiasm! Our mission is ... ; 415 E. N. Water St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 202-0745
Tours & Attractions; Chicago's First Lady Cruises; Welcome aboard Chicago's finest fleet! Choose Chicago's First Lady and the Chicago Architecture Foundation to experience 90-minutes of amazing! The Official Chicago Architecture Foundation River Cruise departs only from the Chicago Riverwalk, just 3-blocks North of Millennium Park at the Southeast corner of the Michigan Ave Bridge at Wacker ... ; 112 E. Wacker Dr. on Chicago's Riverwalk Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (800) 982-2787
Tours & Attractions; Chicago's Women's Park and Gardens; A private and inviting park, filled with fragrant aromas, just south of the Loop.; 1827 S. Indiana Ave. Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 744-6630
Tours & Attractions; City Running Tours; 5k everyday. Personal and group guided run/walk tours. Themed routes include 26.2mile package in 4 days or 4 visits complete with finisher certificate; 201 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (630) 702-9364
Tours & Attractions; City Segway Tours - Chicago; Chicago's first guided Segway tour. Enjoy fascinating stories, fantastic photo ops, superb personal service and the world's coolest machine. Glide with the original -  City Segway Tours. Offering a variety of tour times and options there is an activity for everyone. Day and evening tours are offered seven days ... ; 910 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 819-0186
Tours & Attractions; Columbus Park Refectory; Chicago landmark building surrounded by prairie, rivers and a serene lagoon.; 5701 W. Jackson Blvd. Chicago, IL 60644; Chicago; (312) 742-4838
Tours & Attractions; Daley Civic Center; Picasso Sculpture, "Under the Picasso"; 50 W. Washington St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 603-7980
Tours & Attractions; Eli's Cheesecake World; Visit Eli’s Cheesecake World, a bakery, café and retail store on Chicago’s northwest side, where you can enjoy Eli’s Tasting and Traditions Experience daily at 1pm including a free slice of Eli’s Cheesecake. Group tour packages are also available. Eli’s Cheesecake annual events include Eli’s at Taste of Chicago, ... ; 6701 W. Forest Preserve Dr. Chicago, IL 60634; Chicago; (773) 736-3417
Tours & Attractions; Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago; Visit the Money Museum at the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago. View rare currency and displays of millions of dollars. Detect counterfeit currency and create your own unique dollar bill featuring your portrait. All visitors receive souvenir shredded money. Open Monday thru Friday: 8:30am to 5:00pm. Join us at ... ; 230 S. LaSalle St. Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 322-2400
Tours & Attractions; Frank Lloyd Wright's Robie House; Frank Lloyd Wright's Robie House sparked a revolution in residential architecture whose influence still reverberates today. Designated by the American Institute of Architects as one of the 10 most significant structures of the 20th century, this American treasure is celebrated as one of Chicago's most important works of art. ... ; 5757 S. Woodlawn Ave. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (312) 994-4000
Tours & Attractions; The Friendly Greeter; Sawyer Lahr is a tour guide and sole proprietor of The Friendly Greeter, a boutique destination management company in Chicago equip to staff or refer airport greeters, step-on guides, tour managers/directors (specializing in educational and faith-based groups). The Friendly Greeter also publishes eBook Travel Guides such as Antiquing Andersonville, ... ; Various Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (312) 287-5360
Tours & Attractions; Garfield Park Conservatory; One of the largest gardens under glass in the nation. This conservatory features five permanent collections, an indoor children's garden, outdoor gardens and five annual flower shows. Open daily 9am-5pm. Admission and parking are free.; 300 N. Central Park Ave. Chicago, IL 60624; Chicago; (312) 746-5100
Tours & Attractions; Go Chicago Card; Save up to 55% on Chicago's top attractions. The Go Chicago card is the best way to see all that the city of Chicago has to offer for one low price! Choose from over 25 attractions, tours and museums - including the Shedd Aquarium, Navy Pier, Adler Planetarium and ... ; Purchase online or at participating attractions Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (866) 628-9031
Tours & Attractions; Grant Park Rose Gardens; Lush gardens filled with roses, just steps away from Buckingham Fountain.; Columbus Dr. & Congress Pkwy. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 742-4838
Tours & Attractions; Hershey's Chicago; Experience our unique, interactive retail store and bakery located on Chicago's Magnificent Mile. Operate Hershey's Magnificent Chocolate Works Machine to become a factory worker, with a photo ID and your own assortment of chocolates! Customize a Hershey bar wrapper with a photo (take one in the store or bring ... ; 822 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 337-7711
Tours & Attractions; Hop The Pond; Hop the Pond provides a one stop shop for when young adults come over on a J1 Visa to US. We send them on tours around the city and provide the inside knowledge of Chicago from people that live here.; Chicago, IL; Chicago; (815) 693-7241
Tours & Attractions; John Hancock Observatory; Leisure Visitors & Meeting Professionals: At 1,000ft, John Hancock Observatory offers a unique setting for everything from small gatherings to large groups up to 695, unique cocktail parties to sit down dinners; your clients will not be disappointed. Affordable food and beverage packages have been specifically designed to wow ... ; 875 N. Michigan Ave., 94th Floor Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 751-3681
Tours & Attractions; Joyce Walks Chicago; Hi. I’m Joyce. Thanks for considering taking one of my tours through some of Chicago’s amazing neighborhoods. Joyce Walks Chicago came about because I LOVE CHICAGO. On my tours you will: Interact with public art. Explore culture. Envision architecture. Engage with history. Chicago is a city of unique neighborhoods. ... ; Chicago Chicago, IL 60608; Chicago; (312) 380-9255
Tours & Attractions; Just Sailing Ltd; We offer Private sailing charters for groups of 6 or less on our 30' sailboats, with the safety of a professional captain aboard. Our trips are 2 or 3 hours usually, and occur on Lake Michigan. Its a great way for families to spend quality time together, for friends ... ; 400 E. Monroe Street Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 569-0409
Tours & Attractions; Lincoln Park Conservatory; Peaceful and enchanting gardens in the heart of Lincoln Park, adjacent to the zoo. Open 9am-5pm daily. Free admission.; 2391 N. Stockton Dr. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 742-7736
Tours & Attractions; Lincoln Park Zoo; See roaring lions, playful meerkats and majestic gorillas just minutes from downtown Chicago. Lincoln Park Zoo is free, open and amazing every day of the year. Visitors can go nose-to-nose with gorillas and chimpanzees, howl with red wolves, peer into a black bear den and immerse themselves in the ... ; Cannon Drive at Fullerton Parkway Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 742-2000
Tours & Attractions; Lucky Strike Lanes; Lucky Strike offers Classic American fare with a twist. 18 lanes and 11 billiards tables along with elegant lounge space perfect for your next event!; 322 E. Illinois St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 245-8331
Tours & Attractions; Macy's on State Street; Macy's on State Street (formerly Marshall Field Company flagship store) has been a Chicago destination for more than a century. As the second largest department store in the world, Macy's flagship features 10 floors of retail space, an unparalleled merchandise selection, five unique restaurants and architectural icons including the ... ; 111 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 781-1000
Tours & Attractions; Mercury, Chicago's Skyline Cruiseline; Mercury, Chicago's Skyline Cruiseline delights families of all ages with family-friendly Chicago city tours by boat. Our tours travel the Chicago River to learn fun facts and the unique history of our great city along with city skyline views from Lake Michigan. Welcome aboard and don't forget your camera ... ; 112 E. Wacker Dr. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 332-1353
Tours & Attractions; Metropolitan Limousine; As award-winning transportation specialists since 1972, we are trusted with the guests of Chicago's finest hotels as the in-house carrier, the executives of corporate Chicago, and visitors from around the world. We relish our role as ambassadors for the City of Chicago, and look forward to sharing the best ... ; 1836 S. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 808-8000
Tours & Attractions; MetroWalkz Self-Guided Walking Tours; Discover Chicago at your pace, on your schedule! MetroWalkz' numerous self-guided walking tours with easy-to-use maps and insider narratives make sightseeing a breeze. Current tours include Loop Architecture, Millennium Park, Grant Park / Art Institute, Magnificent Mile, Navy Pier, Museum Campus, Chinatown, Old Town, Gold Coast, West Loop and ... ; 500 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 504-7058
Tours & Attractions; Millennium Park; Millennium Park is an award-winning center for art, music, architecture and landscape design. It's prominent features are the Frank Gehry-designed Jay Pritzker Pavilion, the most sophisticated outdoor concert venue of its kind in the United States; the interactive Crown Fountain by Jaume Plensa; the contemporary Lurie Garden designed by ... ; 201 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 744-6050
Tours & Attractions; Museum of Science and Industry; Specializing in Leisure, Incentive and Student groups….Choose custom tour itineraries in: Art, Architecture, Food, Fashion, Ethnic Neighborhoods, Music, and Theater…or mix it up! We go behind the scenes to the real Chicago with exclusive access to the city’s hidden gems! Enjoy a Cruise on Chicago’s Lakefront, a Progressive Ethnic ... ; 57th Street and Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 684-1414
Tours & Attractions; My Kind of Town Destination Management, Inc.; My Kind of Town Tours & Events has the Chicago and Milwaukee areas covered from A to Z - ARCHITECUTURE to ZOOs, that is. The company was launched just prior to the Bicentennial year in time to share the area history with schools and local adult groups. Today participants ... ; Various Locations Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (847) 295-8221
Tours & Attractions; Mystic Blue Cruises; Historic Navy Pier® is Chicago's lakefront playground with over 50 acres of parks, shops, restaurants, entertainment and attractions. Navy Pier is the Midwest's #1 attractions with more than 8 million visitors a year. Enjoy a ride on the Ferris Wheel, musical carousel, Wave Swinger and miniature golf course. Visit ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (877) 299-7845
Tours & Attractions; Navy Pier; Presenting Hollywood's biggest blockbuster films in IMAX 3D on our soaring 6 story tall screen. Located in the Family Pavilion at the entrance to historic Navy Pier.  Reserve your specific seat at www.imax.com/chicago. Group rates for 10-400, call 312-595-5987. Hours: Mon.- Sun. 10:00am-10:00pm; 600 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 595-5300
Tours & Attractions; Navy Pier IMAX Theatre; Cynthia Noble Private Art Tours & Events offers custom art tours of public art, the Art Institute of Chicago, the Museum of Contemporary Art and neighborhood gallery walks for individuals, families and social or corporate groups.; 700 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 595-5629
Tours & Attractions; Noble Private Art Tours; Odyssey II’s 2 million dollar renovation offers guests an exceptional way to experience an upscale restaurant while cruising along Chicago's world-famous skyline. Odyssey II offers Brunch, Lunch, Dinner, Fireworks and a variety of specialty cruises year-round. From New Year's Eve cruises and Air Water Show events, to July 4th ... ; 840 W. Blackhawk St., #906 Chicago, IL 60642; Chicago; (773) 680-7823
Tours & Attractions; Odyssey Cruises; This authentic Japanese garden with pavilion, moon bridge, Shinto gate and traditional Japanese horticulture was a gift to Chicago from Japan for the 1893 World's Columbian Exposition.; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (866) 826-3463
Tours & Attractions; Osaka Garden; Welcome to Pleasant Prairie Premium Outlets. Featuring 90 stores including Adidas, Banana Republic Factory Store, Brooks Brothers Factory Store, Calvin Klein, Coach, Cole Haan, Gap Outlet, Hugo Boss, J. Crew, Juicy Couture, Lacoste, Michael Kors, Nike, The North Face, Polo Ralph Lauren Factory Store, Puma, Reebok, Restoration Hardware, St ... ; 5900 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60615; Chicago; (312) 747-2474
Tours & Attractions; Pritzker Military Library; Luxury rail travel in historic cars from New Orleans to Chicago. White glove service for the discerning traveler. Chicagoans are familiar with the fascinating history of the Pullman Car Company. Their luxury sleeping accommodations were renowned for their stylish, Art Deco design, plush accommodations and the superb service provided ... ; 104 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 374-9333
Tours & Attractions; Pullman Rail Journeys; See Chicago landmarks and attractions like never before! During your helicopter ride you'll see downtown Chicago, Chicago's historic architecture, Navy Pier, Lake Michigan, Wrigley Field (Chicago Cubs), Willis Tower, Trump Tower, The John Hancock Building, Lincoln Park Zoo, Soldier Field (Chicago Bears), U.S. Cellular Field (Chicago White Sox), Lincoln ... ; 118 S. Clinton St., Ste. 400 Chicago, IL 60661; Chicago; (855) 487-1430
Tours & Attractions; Rotorzen Helicopters, Inc.; Seadog Cruises offers exciting Speedboat Rides, River & Lake Architecture Tours, and Extreme Thrill Rides perfect for a solo traveler or a group of 450. We cruise April through October. Lakefront Firework Speedboat Tours are also available on Wednesday and Saturday, Memorial Day – Labor Day. For groups interested ... ; 6150 S. Laramie Ave. Chicago, IL 60638; Chicago; (708) 924-9277
Tours & Attractions; Seadog Ventures; See Chicago in a new and unique way. Off-duty (active and retired) officers, will show you around our beautiful city. Travel at your own pace, on foot and using public transportation. We'll ride the subway and the "L" (elevated trains). Places you have heard about and would like to ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (866) 636-7737
Tours & Attractions; See Chicago With A Cop; Custom-designed historical and sightseeing tours for out-of-town and local groups. Itineraries, transportation, accommodations, attractions and meals can be provided. Step-on-guide service also available.; Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 315-6374
Tours & Attractions; Segway Experience of Chicago; Join Shoreline for a dramatic Architecture River Tour, exciting Lake Michigan Skyline Tour , Walking Tour or thrilling Fireworks Cruise! Architecture Tours now depart from both Gateway Park at Navy Pier or the northeast corner of the Michigan Avenue Bridge and are led by experienced, entertaining Shoreline guides. Learn ... ; 224 S. Michigan Ave., Ste. 113 Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 663-0600
Tours & Attractions; Shoreline Sightseeing Company; SideTour, a curated marketplace of unique experiences hosted by interesting, passionate locals.; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 222-9328
Tours & Attractions; Skydeck Chicago; The South Shore Cultural Center with castle-like interior and grandiose ballrooms, ornate chandeliers and ample meeting space includes a 65-acre park and surrounding grounds, a golf course, nature sanctuary, bathing beach and an impressive multiuse facility, which originated as the South Shore Country Club.; 233 S. Wacker Dr. Chicago, IL 60606; Chicago; (312) 875-9696
Tours & Attractions; South Shore Cultural Center; A culinary excursion through Chicago's "Little India" neighborhood! Exploring the food, history, culture, architecture and entertainment offered in the South Asian community of Devon Avenue of Chicago's West Rogers Park. The Tour includes: visits to at least 4 food tastings of ethnic eateries, specialty stores and exposure to Indian ... ; 7059 South Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60649; Chicago; (773) 256-0149
Tours & Attractions; Spice of Life Tours; The Spirit of Chicago delivers the most entertaining and unique combination of dining, dancing, entertainment and spectacular views. Groups up to 600 will enjoy buffet dining, an interactive cruise emcee, dance music and incredible skyline views – all for one affordable price. The Spirit of Chicago offers a unique ... ; 2541 W. Devon Ave. Chicago, IL 60659; Chicago; (773) 644-1202
Tours & Attractions; Spirit of Chicago; 3 unforgettable food adventures and chocolate and dessert tours too! Savor the Sweet Flavors of Chicago. Join Tastebud in the city of deep dish pizza, Chicago-style hot dogs and Italian beef. Enjoy tastes of these iconic dishes synonymous with our great city and be introduced to other foods that ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (866) 835-7245
Tours & Attractions; Tastebud Tours; Enjoy a one-of-a-kind walk through time and space in the company of a professional guide brimming with fascinating stories, anecdotes and fun facts about Chicago's history and people. The casually paced adventures provide an opportunity for both locals and visitors to explore varied neighborhoods, culture, food, architecture, shops, bridges, ... ; 550 Kingsbury St., Ste. 218 Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (219) 929-6648
Tours & Attractions; Tours R Us Chicago LLC; Vacations By Rail is the leading seller of rail travel and tours and the trusted authority on train vacations. Select from an assortment of independent rail vacations and escorted rail tours that include stays in Chicago or custom-design a Chicago vacation that includes train travel, premier hotel accommodations and ... ; 2600 N. Lakeview Ave. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 575-3176
Tours & Attractions; Train Vacations | Vacations By Rail; Turismo em Chicago offers city tours in Portuguese designed for the Brazilian market, such as: Architectural tours, walking tours, by nights, and highlights tours. A Turismo em Chicago é uma empresa especializada em serviços turísticos e consultoria para turistas Brasileiros em Chicago e região. Oferecemos city tours em português, ... ; 309 W. Washington St. Chicago, IL 60606; Chicago; (877) 929-7245
Tours & Attractions; Turismo em Chicago; Discover Ukraine's rich culture through colorful Easter eggs, ceramics, costumes, intricate embroidery, and religious artifacts. Learn about the Ukrainian Genocide Famine and the Chernobyl disaster.Please contact the museum at 312-421-8020 to arrange for tour groups.; 400 N. McClurg Ct. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (773) 789-9161
Tours & Attractions; Ukrainian National Museum; Discover unique museums, local bookstores, gothic chapels and architectural masterpieces by world-renowned architects including Wright, Mies and Jahn.; 2249 W. Superior St. Chicago, IL 60612; Chicago; (312) 421-8020
Tours & Attractions; University of Chicago; Viator is the world’s leading resource to discover and book travel activities, providing online and mobile access to more than 15,000 curated trip activities including tours, attractions, shore excursions and private guides, in more than 1,000 destinations worldwide. With more than 350,000 verified reviews plus exclusive videos and insider ... ; 5801 S. Ellis Ave. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 702-8360
Tours & Attractions; Washington Park Refectory; Historical/Architecture, Ghost/Gangster tours, Fireworks Paddle, Skyline Workouts, daily rentals, electric kayaks! Nat'l press/TV, rave reviews.; 5531 S. Russell Dr. Chicago, IL 60615; Chicago; (773) 256-1897
Tours & Attractions; Wateriders Kayak Tours & Rentals Riverwalk; Historic House & Mansion Tours are offered 2 days per week for guests and other visitors including food and drinks. Some tours include music package tours where live music performances include: Blues, Jazz, Rock and Pop Music.; 950 N. Kingsbury St./600 W. Chicago Ave. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 953-9287
Tours & Attractions; Welcome Inn Manor; As Chicago's original architecture boat tour, Wendella has been dedicated to serving Chicago's families, visitors, students, guests and commuters for over 75 years. Family owned and operated for three generations, our mission is to provide you and your family with a safe, comfortable and affordable fun day on the ... ; 4563 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60653; Chicago; (312) 493-2953
Tours & Attractions; Wendella Sightseeing Boats; WhirlyBall combines basketball, floor hockey, lacrosse, and bumper cars all rolled into one! Stop in anytime and enjoy our full-service sports bar featuring giant HD screens and incredible sound, a mouthwatering food menu, three WhirlyBall courts, a multi-level laser tag arena (Chicago & Vernon Hills), a rock-climbing wall (Vernon ... ; 400 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 337-1446
Tours & Attractions; WhirlyBall Chicago; Walk with us along Chicago’s streets–and her alleys, bridges, cemeteries, parks, and rivers–to learn the stories of how Chicago became today’s great city. Because, like Rome, the Windy City wasn’t built in a day! On a WOW Tour, you’re going to get a history lesson. But history like you’ve ... ; 1880 W. Fullerton Ave. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 486-7777
Tours & Attractions; Wild Onion Walks Chicago; Windy City Connection offers a diverse selection of tours to the corporate, social, and student markets. For the corporate market we know when your attendees are done with business, they want to explore and kick back. That’s' why no program is complete without great tours! As a leading Destination ... ; 1423 W. Hollywood Ave. Chicago, IL 60660; Chicago; (773) 960-5470
Museums; Adler Planetarium; The Adler Planetarium, the first planetarium in the Western Hemisphere, fuels the imagination with exhibitions, leading-edge technology, hands-on activities for the family and three theaters. Make sure to catch a space show in the transformed Grainger Sky Theater, which offers audiences the most immersive, technologically enhanced theater experience ever ... ; 1300 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 922-7827
Museums; Alderman Exhibitions; Alderman Exhibitions is a contemporary art gallery featuring emerging and established artists offering photography, painting, sculpture and editions.; 1138 W. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60607; Chicago; (312) 208-9001
Museums; Art Institute of Chicago; Traveling to Chicago? No trip is complete without a visit to the city’s #1 museum, also voted #1 Chicago attraction by TripAdvisor—out of 300 venues! Explore America’s greatest collection of Impressionist paintings, including world-famous works by Monet, Renoir, Seurat, and Van Gogh. Then discover the critically acclaimed Modern Wing, ... ; 111 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 443-3600
Museums; Charnley-Persky House; Guided tours of this Louis Sullivan and Frank Lloyd Wright designed Gold Coast residence.  Wed. at noon and Sat. at 10am.; 1365 N. Astor St. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 915-0105
Museums; Chicago Architecture Foundation; The Chicago Architecture Foundation (CAF) offers over 85 exciting tours of Chicago including the #1 architecture tour in the city: the Chicago Architecture Foundation River Cruise aboard Chicago's First Lady Cruises. Our other tours include walking, bus, bike, and Segway tours. Space fills quickly, so book now at http://www.architecture.org ... ; 224 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 922-3432
Museums; Chicago Children's Museum; Want world-class fun? Splash, climb, build, learn and explore at the award-winning Chicago Children’s Museum, located at Navy Pier! It’s three floors of fun for children and families. Climb on a ship, hide in a treehouse, construct a building, dam up a river, drive a fire truck, tinker with ... ; 700 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 527-1000
Museums; Chicago CityPASS; Save 49% off Chicago’s best attractions, plus skip lines. Chicago CityPASS includes VIP admission to: Shedd Aquarium, The Field Museum, Skydeck Chicago, Adler Planetarium OR Art Institute of Chicago and Museum of Science and Industry OR John Hancock Observatory. Valid 9-days. Cost: Adult $89 (value $174); Child (3-11) $79. ... ; Purchase from participating attractions Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (208) 787-4300
Museums; Chicago Cultural Center; Chicago's acclaimed landmark home of the arts. Daily programs and exhibitions covering a wide range of the performing, visual and literary arts are presented by the Chicago Department of Cultural Affairs. See the world's largest Tiffany stained-glass dome. Hours: Mon.-Thurs. 10am-7pm, Fri. 10am-6pm, Sat. 10am-5pm, Sun. 11am-5pm. Closed holidays. ; 78 E. Washington St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 744-6630
Museums; Chicago Gallery News; A central source for information about the area's galleries, museums, art events and resources. We offer galley guides, maps, interviews, etc.; 213 W. Institute Pl. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 649-0064
Museums; Chicago History Museum; The Chicago History Museum offers exhibitions and public programs that illuminate the city's past, engage the city's present, and point to Chicago's future. Vivian Maier's Chicago explores the city through the eyes of the nanny turned photographer who wowed the world with breathtaking images of everyday urban America. Maier's ... ; 1601 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 642-4600
Museums; Chicago International Art, Antique & Jewelry Show; Backed by substantial momentum, the Palm Beach Show Group proudly announces the seventh addition to its portfolio of fine art, antique and jewelry shows: The inaugural Chicago International Art, Antique & Jewelry Show, set to take place next Spring at the Navy Pier—April, 24-28, 2014. The Chicago Show will ... ; Navy Pier Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (561) 822-5440
Museums; City Gallery at the Historic Water Tower; Located in one of Chicago's most popular landmarks, the new City Gallery features photographs of Chicago by Chicago photographers.; 806 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 742-0808
Museums; Clarke House Museum; If Chicago has a love of architecture, it probably begins here with Chicago's oldest domestic structure, a Greek Revival house built in 1836 by the Henry B. Clarke Family, a middle-class family life in Chicago during the city's formative years before the Civil War. Tours Wed.-Sun. noon and 2pm. ... ; 1827 S. Indiana Ave. Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 326-1480
Museums; Driehaus Museum; Steps away from Chicago’s Michigan Avenue, the Richard H. Driehaus Museum offers visitors a fascinating view of one of the few remaining examples of the palatial homes erected by the wealthy of America’s Gilded Age. The galleries, elegantly furnished with period pieces selected from the Driehaus Collection, are presented ... ; 40 E. Erie Street Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 482-8933
Museums; DuSable Museum of African American History; Celebrating over 50 years of sharing history, DuSable Museum of African American History is the nation's first independent museum dedicated to the collection, preservation and study of the history and culture of Africans and Americans of African descent. Exhibits, concerts, films, children's events and literary discussions are just a ... ; 740 E. 56th Pl. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 947-0600
Museums; EXPO CHICAGO; EXPO CHICAGO/2013, The International Exposition of Contemporary and Modern Art. Situated at Navy Pier’s Festival Hall (600 E. Grand Avenue), Sept. 19 – 22, this four-day art event features over 120 leading international galleries and offers diverse programming including /DIALOGUES, IN/SITU and EXPOSURE. Under the leadership of President and ... ; 372 W. Ontario St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 867-9220
Museums; Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago; Visit the Money Museum at the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago. View rare currency and displays of millions of dollars. Detect counterfeit currency and create your own unique dollar bill featuring your portrait. All visitors receive souvenir shredded money. Open Monday thru Friday: 8:30am to 5:00pm. Adult visitors must ... ; 230 S. LaSalle St. Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 322-2400
Museums; The Field Museum; Leisure Visitors: Discover Sue, the world's largest and most complete T. rex ever found! Descend into an Egyptian tomb and see 23 Egyptian mummies and 5,000 year-old hieroglyphics, shrink to 1/100th of your natural size and get a bug's-eye view in Underground Adventure, come nose-to-nose with the man-eating lions ... ; 1400 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 922-9410
Museums; Glessner House Museum; H. H. Richardson designed architectural treasure. Guided tours Wed - Sun at 1pm & 3pm. $10/adult, $9/senior, $6/child. Combo price w/Clarke House.; 1800 S. Prairie Ave. Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 326-1480
Museums; International Museum of Surgical Science; Housed in a historic mansion on Lake Shore Drive, the International Museum of Surgical Science spans the history of surgery by means of art, books, medical instruments and artifacts. The Museum’s collections and exhibitions portray the mysteries, breakthroughs, failures, and milestones that have shaped modern surgical science. Our four ... ; 1524 N. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 642-6502
Museums; Life Force Arts Foundation; The mission of Life Force Arts Foundation (LFA) is to advance the field of spiritual art through artistically excellent exhibits, events and publications that explore the connection of art and spirituality. We define spiritual art as visual, literary or performing art that flows from spiritual practice, strives to connect ... ; 1609 W. Belmont Ave. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 327-7224
Museums; Lillstreet Art Center; Visit Chicago’s largest visual arts center. Founded in 1975, Lillstreet Art Center is a large community of artists and students working side-by-side in a friendly environment, which encourages and inspires artistic growth in the individual. Our center on Ravenswood Ave., boasts state-of-art equipment and more than 800 art classes ... ; 4401 N. Ravenswood Ave. Chicago, IL 60640; Chicago; (773) 769-4226
Museums; McCormick Bridgehouse & Chicago River Museum; The McCormick Bridgehouse & Chicago River Museum celebrates Chicago’s river and world-famous movable bridges by shining light on their significance to the city. Beginning at river level and spiraling five stories up, this vertical adventure provides a one-of-a-kind opportunity to explore a historic landmark bridgehouse. The discovery begins at ... ; 376 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 977-0227
Museums; Museum of Broadcast Communications; Mission of MBC: To collect, preserve and present historic and contemporary radio and television content as well as educate, inform & entertain the public through its archives, public programs, screenings, exhibits, publications & online access to its resources.; 360 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60654-5411; Chicago; (312) 245-8200
Museums; Museum of Contemporary Art; One of Chicago's most sophisticated sites. Guests can sip champagne while strolling through the sculpture garden and terrace overlooking Lake Michigan or listen to music while viewing some of the world's most celebrated art. Take a free, guided tour, stroll through our grand, barrel-vaulted galleries overlooking Lake Michigan and ... ; 220 E. Chicago Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 280-2660
Museums; Museum of Science and Industry; The Museum of Science and Industry is the largest science museum in the Western Hemisphere! Housed in the only remaining building from the 1893 World’s Fair, MSI is a Chicago must-see! You’ll experience 14 acres of hands-on exhibits and have the chance to stand before a 40-foot tornado; climb ... ; 57th Street and Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 684-1414
Museums; National Hellenic Museum; A premiere institution that fosters a deeper connection to American history and culture through the experiences of Americans of Greek origin.; 333 S. Halsted St. Chicago, IL 60661; Chicago; (312) 655-1234
Museums; Peggy Notebaert Nature Museum; The Peggy Notebaert Nature Museum serves as an urban gateway to nature and science. Located in an eco-friendly building amidst abundant wildlife and nature in Lincoln Park, hands-on exhibitions allow visitors of all ages to connect with regional wildlife and public programs that inspire green living and sustainability. Interact ... ; 2430 N. Cannon Dr. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 755-5100
Museums; Pritzker Military Library; Across the street from Millennium Park and the Art Institute of Chicago, the Pritzker Military Library is open to the public with live events and a collection of books, films, and gallery exhibits that tell the story of the Citizen Soldier in American military history.; 104 S. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 374-9333
Museums; Shedd Aquarium; At Shedd Aquarium, animals connect you to the living world, inspiring you to make a difference. From whales to snails, tarantulas to turtles, you’ll meet 32,500 creatures from aquatic habitats around the world. Explore Shedd’s Abbott Oceanarium, where you can get face to face with beluga whales, dolphins, sea ... ; 1200 S. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 939-2438
Museums; Smart Museum of Art, The University of Chicago; As the fine arts museum of the University of Chicago, the Smart is home to thought-provoking exhibitions and an exquisite collection of ancient, modern, and contemporary art from across the globe. Free and open to the public.; 5550 S. Greenwood Ave. Chicago, IL 60637; Chicago; (773) 702-0200
Museums; The Smith Museum of Stained Glass Windows; Free and open year-round to the public during Navy Pier operating hours Mon. - Thurs. 10am - 8 pm; Fri.-Stat 10am-10pm; Sun. 10am - 7pm. Free public tours are available at 2:30pm every Fri. Call 312-595-5024 for more information.; 600 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 595-7437
Museums; Swedish American Museum; You don’t have to be Swedish to visit Chicago’s Swedish-American Museum! The Museum has something for everyone—an art gallery, immigration exhibit, children’s museum, genealogy center, and a gift shop featuring a beautiful selection of handcrafted Scandinavian gifts. Established in 1976, the Swedish American Museum is a bustling center of ... ; 5211 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60640; Chicago; (773) 728-8111
Museums; Ukrainian National Museum; Discover Ukraine's rich culture through colorful Easter eggs, ceramics, costumes, intricate embroidery, and religious artifacts. Learn about the Ukrainian Genocide Famine and the Chernobyl disaster.; 2249 W. Superior St. Chicago, IL 60612; Chicago; (312) 421-8020
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Auditorium Theatre of Roosevelt University; A historic Landmark, the Auditorium Theatre of Roosevelt University offers world class entertainment for a world class city. The theatre is proud to serve as the resident home of The Joffrey Ballet, as well as the Chicago venue of choice for all major domestic and international dance companies. In ... ; 50 E. Congress Pkwy. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 341-2310
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Blue Man Group; Blue Man Group is a wildly popular entertainment phenomenon currently in an open-ended run. The production provides its audience with a unique and thrilling multi-sensory experience that fuses innovative theatrical spectacle and powerful original music with hilarious comedy, art, vaudeville and science to create a performance experience unlike any ... ; 3133 N. Halsted St. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 348-4000
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Broadway In Chicago; Broadway In Chicago brings Broadway's biggest shows to Chicago's finest theaters. On the stages of the Oriental Theatre, Cadillac Palace Theatre, Bank of America Theatre, Broadway Playhouse and the Auditorium Theatre of Roosevelt University see shows direct from Broadway and world premieres destined for Broadway. Current/Upcoming offerings include: THE ... ; 17 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 977-1701
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Chicago Cultural Center; Daily programs & exhibitions covering a wide range of the performing & visual arts, presented by the Department of Cultural Affairs and Special Events; 78 E. Washington St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 744-6630
Theaters &	Performing Arts; The Chicago Theatre; The landmark Chicago Theatre is likely the city's most iconic venue, and its famous C-H-I-C-A-G-O marquee lights up State Street every evening. Located in Chicago's Loop, it hosts everything from concerts comedians to special events, film premieres. Its convenient downtown location makes it close to hotels, restaurants and parking. ... ; 175 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 462-6300
Theaters &	Performing Arts; ComedySportz Theatre; Now in our 26th season, ComedySportz is a unique blend of fast and funny improv comedy that is appropriate for all ages. Two teams of improvisers play short-form improv games in front of a referee and the audience votes for the team that makes them laugh harder. You, the ... ; 929 W. Belmont Ave. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 549-8080
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Dinner Detective Murder Mystery Dinner Show; Now America's Largest Murder Mystery Dinner show, our tickets start at $61.95 and include a four course sit down dinner, full cash bar, music, clues and prizes for the Top Detective. Show runs every Saturday night and select Fridays.; 163 E. Walton Pl. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (866) 496-0535
Theaters &	Performing Arts; FlySpace Chicago; FlySpaceConsortium In a theater, fly space is the volume above the stage where scenery and lighting hang together ready to be lowered into view. Some call it ‘heaven.’ In Chicago, FlySpace is a new strategic partnership conceived and launched by four female-led dance organizations, The Dance Collective, Hedwig Dances, ... ; 2010 N. Damen Ave. Chicago, IL 60647; Chicago; (773) 489-5069
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Goodman Theatre; Goodman Theatre, Chicago’s oldest and largest not-for-profit theater, has won international renown for the quality of productions, the depth and diversity of artistic leadership, and the excellence of its many community and educational programs. The Goodman is committed to producing both classic and contemporary works, giving full voice to ... ; 170 N. Dearborn St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 443-3800
Theaters &	Performing Arts; The Harris Theater for Music and Dance; Situated in the distinctive setting of Millennium Park, the Harris Theater is an artistic home for the very best of Chicago's music & dance companies.; 205 E. Randolph Dr. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 334-2400
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Hot Tix; Conveniently located in the Loop and along the Magnificent Mile, Hot Tix theater geniuses offer half price theater tickets up to six days in advance of the performance. View this week's list of 1/2 price shows at HotTix.org.; 72 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 977-9483
Theaters &	Performing Arts; The Joffrey Ballet; Chicago's premier ballet company.; Joffrey Tower, 10 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 739-0120
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Late Nite Catechism; A Chicago original and international hit, LATE NITE CATECHISM is celebrating a record-breaking 20 seasons! The sequel, PUT THE NUNS IN CHARGE!, has its own long-standing tradition. If you have seen these delightful comedies once, twice or three times (or more), you understand their appeal. Because of their interactive ... ; 4343 N. Clarendon Ave. Chicago, IL 60613; Chicago; (773) 388-0730
Theaters &	Performing Arts; League of Chicago Theatres; The Chicago theatre community boasts over 250 professional theatre companies with more than five million attendees per year. Chicago is a theatre town. The League of Chicago Theatres works to keep Chicago a place where theatre thrives. Whether you call yourself a Chicagoan or are just visiting for the ... ; 17 N. Wabash St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 554-9800
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Lookingglass Theatre Company; Recipient of the 2011 Tony Award for Outstanding Regional Theatre, Lookingglass Theatre Company has been redefining the theatrical experience in Chicago for more than twenty years. Lookingglass' intimate 200-seat theater is located inside the historic Pumping Station on Michigan Avenue. Original scripts created by Lookingglass’ artistic ensemble have been ... ; 821 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 337-0665
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Million Dollar Quartet; Chicago's smash hit musical inspired by the famed 1956 Sun Studios recording session that brought together legendary Rock N' Roll icons Johnny Cash, Jerry Lee Lewis, Carl Perkins and Elvis Presley. Hear the greatest hits from these music legends including "Blue Suede Shoes", "Great Balls of Fire" and more. ... ; Apollo Theater Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 935-6100
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Riverfront Theater; Riverfront Theater is Chicago's newest destination for music, theater, dance, spectacles and more. The 20,000 sq.ft., 59 foot, temperature-controlled, tented auditorium is the cornerstone of a 80,000 sq. ft. entertainment complex.; 650 W. Chicago Ave. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 595-0611
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Shen Yun Show Chicago; Shen Yun Show features colorful and exhilarating performances of classical Chinese dance and music inspired by 5000 years of traditional culture. The 2013 Shen Yun Show Chicago dates are: Friday, May 10, 7:30 p.m.; Saturday, May 11, 2 :00 p.m. & 8:00 p.m., and Sunday, May 12, 2:00 p.m. ; Cadillac Palace Theatre Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (800) 515-3468
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Steppenwolf Theatre Company; Steppenwolf Theatre Company is America’s longest standing, most distinguished ensemble theater, producing nearly 700 performances and events annually in its three Chicago theater spaces—the 515-seat Downstairs Theatre, the 299-seat Upstairs Theatre and the 80-seat Garage Theatre. Formed in 1976 by a collective of actors, Steppenwolf has grown into an ... ; 1650 N. Halsted St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 335-1650
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Theater on the Lake; Each summer, the Chicago Park District's open-air stage is home to the "best dramatic, comedic and innovative performances the city of Chicago has to offer."; 2401 N. Lake Shore Dr. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 742-7994
Theaters &	Performing Arts; Tommy Gun's Garage; Psst...Do you know da password? Audience interactive "Speakeasy" offering a Roaring 20's Musical Comedy Review with da Gangsters, da Flappers and You! You'll be served great food and hooch (uh, dat's liquor) by da Gangsters and da Flappers. Open Thurs.-Sun. Nov.-April. Tues.-Sun. May-Oct. Res. Req.; 2114 S. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 225-0273
Shopping; "Nuts on Clark"; For 35 years world famous Chicago icon offering popcorn, nuts & fine chocolate. Also located at O'Hare & Midway airport & Union Station. Order online.; 3830 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60613; Chicago; (773) 549-6622
Shopping; 900 North Michigan Shops; Recognized as the lead anchor of Chicago's vibrant Magnificent Mile shopping district, 900 North Michigan Shops is a destination for style and sophistication unparalleled anywhere else in the Midwest. This architecturally stunning property features a 6-level Bloomingdale's and over 70 upscale shops that include a line-up of world-renowned brands ... ; 900 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 915-3916
Shopping; Altmans Shoes and Boots for Men; Chicago's premier men's footwear shop carries an unsurpassed collection of men's shoes, boots, and accessories. Sizes range from 5-20, widths 3A-6E. Manufacturers include: Allen Edmonds, Bacco Bucci, Bass, Belvedere, Birkenstock, Blundstone, Bostonian, Bruno Magli, Caterpillar, Chippewa, Clark, Cole Haan, Columbia, Dan Post, David, Donald J. Pliner, Double H, Dr. ... ; 120 W. Monroe St. Chicago, IL 60603; Chicago; (312) 332-0667
Shopping; American Girl Place; Discover why American Girl Place® Chicago is more than just a store—it’s a place for her imagination to soar! She’ll love exploring the worlds of her favorite characters filled with doll collections, books, outfits and more. From inspiring historical characters to the contemporary Girl of the Year® dolls, she's ... ; 835 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 943-9400
Shopping; Arts & Artisans, LLC; One of Downtown's largest showcases of contemporary American art and jewelry, providing a vast collection of art media including stained and blown glass, metal and wood sculpture, artfully crafted jewelry, functional and decorative ceramics, finely woven wearables and exquisite paintings and prints.; 321 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 541-1951
Shopping; Bentley Gold Coast/ Rolls Royce / Lamborghini Gold Coast; Automotive Showcase featuring Ultra-High-End and Exotic automobiles. We ship nationwide and international. A car lover's dream come true!; 834 N. Rush St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 280-4848
Shopping; Block 37; Opening Fall 2009, this new landmark development on State St. will feature first-to-Chicago retailers, signature dining and entertainment venues within a five-story atrium. The center has direct access to the CTA Red and Blue Lines as well as Chicago's extensive pedway system. Mon.-Sat. 10am-8pm; Sun. 11am-6pm.; Block 37 Management Office Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 261-4738
Shopping; Bloomingdale's; The Chicago flagship store features six levels of upscale shopping including men's, women's and children's clothing, shoes and cosmetics. Spring 2013 will bring an expanded and completely revamped Women's Shoe department on the third floor featuring a new space and representing the latest in women's fashion. The store will ... ; 900 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 440-4596
Shopping; Burberry; “As the original British Luxury brand, Burberry offers an extensive selection of outerwear, clothing, sportswear and gifts for men and women. Hours: Mon.-Sat. 10am-7pm; Sun. 12pm-6pm. AE, V, MC, DC, CB, DS, JCB.”; 540 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 787-2500
Shopping; Burton Snowboards Flagship Store; Burton's multilevel flagship store features a knowledgeable staff and the latest gear from Burton. Shop boards, outerwear, luggage, apparel and more.; 56 E. Walton St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 202-7900
Shopping; Candyality; Candyality is known as the sweetest destination in Chicago! Local chain of candy stores, Candyality carries thousands of sweet treats, bulk candies, chocolates, and a retro selection that will take you back in time! Candyality is on a mission to uncover the universal connection to your confections. Shop our ... ; 835 N Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (773) 472-7800
Shopping; Chicago Chinatown Chamber of Commerce; Chicago's Chinatown is a popular tourist destination with Chinese restaurants, gift shops, grocery stores, Chinese pharmacies, a museum... offering a rich blend of heritage, culture, people, businesses, and activities. The mission of the Chinatown Chamber of Commerce is to improve and expand business opportunities and to educate others on ... ; 2169B S. China Pl. Chicago, IL 60616; Chicago; (312) 326-5320
Shopping; Clarks; Clarks offers a wide array of comfortable, stylish footwear and accessories for every occasion.; 845 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 335-9114
Shopping; Columbia Sportswear; Columbia is a leading innovator in the global outdoor apparel, footwear, accessories and equipment industry. Come shop the largest selection of Columbia.; 830 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 951-2679
Shopping; gallery37 Retail Store; The Gallery 37 Center for the Arts provides a venue for youth, families and adults to participate in several innovative arts programs, including After School Matters and the Chicago Public Schools’ Advanced Arts Education Program. The Center also hosts World Kitchen, Storefront Theater, Downtown Sound Gallery, artScape Chicago, Gallery ... ; 66 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 744-7267
Shopping; Garmin International; Navigate to the Garmin Store + experience the latest GPS technology not just for drivers but for runners, golfers, bikers, hikers, boaters + aviators.; 663 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 787-3221
Shopping; Garrett Popcorn Shops; The Original, Handcrafted Gourmet Popcorn For more than 60 years, Garrett Popcorn Shops® has attracted passionate fans around the world with the enticing aroma and taste of their handcrafted, gourmet popcorn. Every batch of Garrett Popcorn is handmade throughout the day in old-fashioned copper kettles using secret family recipes ... ; 625 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 944-2630
Shopping; Giftbar; Featured in Elle, Lucky Magazine, Refinery29, Daily Candy and many other fashion forward publications, Giftbar is the only curated directory of over 150 boutiques, specialty stores and restaurants in Chicago. Not only can you research and plan your next shopping trip to select neighborhoods in Chicago, but you can ... ; 1802 W. Berteau Ave. Chicago, IL 60613; Chicago; (773) 661-2259
Shopping; Hershey's Chicago; Experience our unique, interactive retail store and bakery located on Chicago's Magnificent Mile.  Operate Hershey's Magnificent Chocolate Works Machine to become a factory worker, with a photo ID and your own assortment of chocolates! Customize a Hershey bar wrapper with a photo (take one in the store or bring ... ; 822 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 337-7711
Shopping; Lillstreet Art Center; Visit Chicago’s largest visual arts center. Founded in 1975, Lillstreet Art Center is a large community of artists and students working side-by-side in a friendly environment, which encourages and inspires artistic growth in the individual. Our center on Ravenswood Ave., boasts state-of-art equipment and more than 800 art classes ... ; 4401 N. Ravenswood Ave. Chicago, IL 60640; Chicago; (773) 769-4226
Shopping; LOFT; LOFT is committed to providing women approachable fashion with on-trend, stylish pieces all at affordable price points. LOFT delivers on the promise to be her trusted stylist, giving her ideas and inspiration to make every look uniquely her own. LOFT on Michigan Avenue, is a two-story concept store complete ... ; 670 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 915-0410
Shopping; Macy's; Our Magnificent Mile location offers eight floors of designer fashions, accessories, shoes, cosmetics and house wares. Extended holiday hours. 835 N. Michigan Ave., 312-335-7700, www.macys.com.; 835 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 335-7700
Shopping; Macy's on State Street; Macy's on State Street (formerly Marshall Field Company flagship store) has been a Chicago destination for more than a century. As the second largest department store in the world, Macy's flagship features 10 floors of retail space, an unparalleled merchandise selection, five unique restaurants and architectural icons including the ... ; 111 N. State St. Chicago, IL 60602; Chicago; (312) 781-1000
Shopping; Mary Mary Gifts; Mary Mary is Chicago's most unique gift and home furnishings boutique, located just steps from the Magnificent Mile and tucked away in a 133 year old Brownstone. Whether you are shopping for men, women or children, you will always find the perfect gift at Mary Mary!; 706 N. Dearborn St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 654-8100
Shopping; The Merchandise Mart; 200+ luxury showrooms for kitchen, bath & building products, custom home furnishings, fabrics, floor & wall coverings, lighting, antiques & more.; 222 Merchandise Mart Plz. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 527-4141
Shopping; Nordstrom Michigan Avenue; Nordstrom, one of the nation's leading fashion specialty retailers, offers its Michigan Avenue customers 271,000 sq. ft., four levels of contemporary and classic shoes, clothing, and accessories for the entire family. A wide range of special services and amenities are available including personal stylists, concierge, in-store alterations, shoe shine ... ; 55 E. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 464-1515
Shopping; Pastoral Artisan Cheese, Bread & Wine; Pastoral Artisan Cheese, Bread & Wine, is an award-winning European-inspired neighborhood cheese, specialty food and wine shop offering the highest quality, cut-to-order domestic and international specialty cheeses, freshly baked breads, perfectly chosen accompaniments and small production wines, along with hand-crafted, cheese loving beers. Over time we have become known ... ; 53 E. Lake St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (773) 472-4781
Shopping; Randolph Street Market Festival; As featured in Travel & Leisure, Lucky Magazine, and the Wall Street Journal, Chicago's Randolph Street Market is THE destination for antique collectors, merchandisers, decorators, fashionistas & style setters from around the globe, featuring the most spectacular array of vintage & modern decorative objects, home furnishings, art, jewelry & ... ; 1340 W. Washington St. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 666-1200
Shopping; Richard Bennett Custom Tailors; Chicago's oldest and most recognized genuine Custom Tailor - hand-crafting garments of distinction for Men and Women in our own downtown shop since 1929. From suits to shirts, each item fits perfectly, wears well and looks great for every business or social occasion.; 175 W. Jackson Blvd. Chicago, IL 60604; Chicago; (312) 913-1100
Shopping; Saks Fifth Avenue Chicago; Known for its service- featuring the best fashion the world has to offer in women's, men's, and children's apparel, plus accessories. Personal shopping service available.; 700 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 944-6500
Shopping; The Shops at North Bridge; Sprawling six chic blocks in the heart of the Michigan Avenue district, The Shops at North Bridge is Chicago's most stylish shopping and dining destination. Featuring a four-level shopping center anchored by a flagship Nordstrom and more than 50 world-class retailers including BOSS Hugo Boss, Stuart Weitzman, Wolford, Louis ... ; 520 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 327-2300
Shopping; The Spa at Trump®; A tranquil haven, The Spa at Trump is the perfect place to relax and rejuvenate. Signature Kate Sommerville services leave you red carpet ready.; 401 N. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 588-8020
Shopping; Terry's Toffee, Inc.; Terry's Toffee offers 17 remarkable flavors of Award-winning gourmet toffee, including two No Sugar Added flavors safe for Type 1 & 2 diabetics. All flavors are GLUTEN FREE, except the Mazel Toffee & Asian Accent. Taste our newest product, "Amazing Wackerpop", fresh popcorn smothered in our delicious toffee and ... ; 1117 W. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60642; Chicago; (312) 733-2700
Shopping; Trunk Club; Based in Chicago's rapidly growing startup scene, Trunk Club is a personalized clothing service for men, offering designer clothing to customers without any of the hassles of shopping in stores or online. Men simply tell their Trunk Club stylist their fit, style and size preferences, and the company ships ... ; 325 W. Ohio St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (866) 406-2235
Shopping; Tumi; Tumi is the leading international brand of business, lifestyle and travel accessories, catering to successful professionals, influential thought leaders, celebrities and discerning travelers around the world.; 645 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 787-3096
Shopping; Water Tower Place; At the pinnacle of Chicago's famed Magnificent Mile, Water Tower Place is Chicago's premier shopping destination. Its stunning eight-level atrium features American Girl Place, Macy's, Broadway In Chicago's Broadway Playhouse and more than 100 of your favorite stores, spas and restaurants, plus a mix of distinctive specialty shops and ... ; 835 N. Michigan Ave. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 440-3166
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Blue Chicago; Blue Chicago is world-renowned offering the best of Chicago's blues musicians and vocalists performing in an intimate and friendly atmosphere. Conveniently located in the River North Entertainment district near the major hotels. Open 7 nights a week from 8 p.m. music beginning at 9 p.m.; 536 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 661-0100
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Buddy Guy's Legends; Chicago's premier blues club now at it's new location, owned by Buddy Guy; local and national blues bands every night. Enjoy a full menu and bar.; 700 S. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 427-1190
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Castle Chicago; Chicago's ultimate nightlife experience with World Class sound, lighting and special FX; 632 N. Dearborn St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 337-3836
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Chi Bar; Chi Bar is located within the Sheraton Chicago Hotel & Towers in the heart of downtown Chicago. Designed by renowned architect, Jeffrey Beers, Chi Bar's d?cor boasts contemporary shades of cobalt blue and amber, deep mahogany wood paneling, plush leather chairs and sofas, and floor-to-ceiling jeweled toned windows offering ... ; 301 E. North Water St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 329-7005
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; City Winery; City Winery is Chicago's first operational winery, private event space, 300-seat concert hall and restaurant.; 1200 W. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60607; Chicago; (312) 733-9463
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; ComedySportz Theatre; Now in our 26th season, ComedySportz is a unique blend of fast and funny improv comedy that is appropriate for all ages. Two teams of improvisers play short-form improv games in front of a referee and the audience votes for the team that makes them laugh harder. You, the ... ; 929 W. Belmont Ave. Chicago, IL 60657; Chicago; (773) 549-8080
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Cuvee Ultra Lounge; As the name suggests, every element of this ultra-lounge was considered and meticulous selections were made to create an intimate space for Chicago's elite, including a champagne list fit for a mature and sophisticated palate. Available seven days a week.; 308 W. Erie St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 202-9221
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Ditka's Restaurant; Chicago's own Johnny Vincent sings the sounds of Frank Sintara, Louie Armstrong, Johnny Cash, and many, many, more. Every Tuesday through Saturday with no cover charge.; 100 E. Chestnut St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 587-8989
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Drawing Room; This Michelin-rated restaurant features a seasonal American Contemporary menu, but the cocktail list is the star. An award-winning team of Master Bartenders craft perfectly balanced cocktails from an extensive selection of small batch spirits. For a unique experience, grab a seat at the bar and soak in the knowledge ... ; 937 N. Rush St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 266-2694
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Fadó Irish Pub; The only venue in River North with LIVE music and no cover charge....every Friday & Saturday from 10pm.; 100 W. Grand Ave. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 836-0066
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Grid; At this upscale sports bar you will enter a world of class and comfort. From the vent less fireplaces to the playful food no other bar compares.; 351 W. Hubbard St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 321-1351
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; House of Blues; Chicago's premier restaurant and concert venue is a unique setting for any private event. The soaring splendor of a European Opera House combined with the down-home aura of a juke-joint make House of Blues a wonderfully unique entertainment experience. Food, music, shopping and a variety of event space options ... ; 329 N. Dearborn Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 923-2000
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Howl at the Moon; Howl at the Moon is a live music venue providing dueling piano show entertainment 7 nights a week! It's a singing & dancing interactive form of entertainment where you name the songs you want to hear and we play them as you sing along!; 26 W. Hubbard St. Chicago, IL 60610; Chicago; (312) 863-7427
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Kerryman Bar and Restaurant; The Kerryman offers a sleek but warm vibe. Irish born and trained Executive Chef Damien Moloney creates an upscale menu that features comfort dishes.; 661 N. Clark St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 335-8121
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Kingston Mines Chicago Blues Center; Chicago Blues Center. Two bands on two stages provide continuous music seven nights a week at this renowned Blues mecca. Full kitchen serving award winning barbecue ribs, fried or blackened catfish, wings, burgers and more till late night for your dining pleasure. Kingston Mines-where legends are made since 1968. ... ; 2548 N. Halsted St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 477-4647
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Lucky Strike Lanes; Specialty cocktails and classic American fare in the upscale bowling/billiards lounge and sports bar with 18 projection-screen and 22 plasma TVs.; 322 E. Illinois St. Chicago, IL 60611; Chicago; (312) 245-8331
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Lyric Opera of Chicago; Lyric Opera of Chicago is one of the world's greatest opera companies. It is renowned internationally for its artistic excellence and breath-taking productions. Lyric's performances feature wonderful music and the greatest singers in the world performing without microphones! The 3,563 seat theatre is the second-largest opera auditorium in North ... ; 20 N. Wacker Dr., Ste. 860 Chicago, IL 60606; Chicago; (312) 332-2244
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; M Lounge; M Lounge is an intimate martini lounge that is warmly lit with candles, sconces and blue lighting which illuminates the vast selection of spirits. Honey and brown walls, burgundy velvet curtains, comfy sofas, table seating in hues of chocolates & sage, and a 28 ft walnut bar make this ... ; 1520 S. Wabash Ave. Chicago, IL 60605; Chicago; (312) 447-0201
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Million Dollar Quartet; Chicago's smash hit musical inspired by the famed 1956 Sun Studios recording session that brought together legendary Rock N' Roll icons Johnny Cash, Jerry Lee Lewis, Carl Perkins and Elvis Presley. Hear the greatest hits from these music legends including "Blue Suede Shoes", "Great Balls of Fire" and more. ... ; Apollo Theater Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (773) 935-6100
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Redhead Piano Bar; • No cover. • Live music seven nights a week. • Fun and eclectic clientele. • Voted “Best Over 30’s Single Scene” and “Best Live Music Venue” by Citysearch.com Readers. • Voted Concierge Preferred Favorite Nightlife Award by Chicago Concierge. • Open 20 years and still rocking. • 40+ ... ; 16 W. Ontario St. Chicago, IL 60654; Chicago; (312) 640-1000
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; The Second City; Celebrating over 50 years as the birthplace of Chicago-style improv and sketch comedy, The Second City has launched the careers of John Belushi, Mike Myers, Tina Fey, Bill Murray, Stephen Colbert, Steve Carell and many others. Schedule is as follows:Mon.-Thurs. 8pm; Fri. 8pm and 11pm; Sat. 8pm and 11pm; ... ; 1616 N. Wells St. Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 337-3992
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Sports Corner; Sports Corner is a three floor sports bar located across the street from Wrigley Field featuring outdoor roof deck and second floor al fresco dining.; 956 W. Addison St. Chicago, IL 60613; Chicago; (773) 929-1441
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; Tavern at the Park; The Tavern Tree House is Chicago's hottest roof top deck. Spectacular views of Millennium Park and historical Michigan Avenue. Open year round with a glass enclosed atrium section. Come and enjoy your favorite game while relaxing in overstuffed couches or have a full dinner while taking in the view. ... ; 130 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601; Chicago; (312) 552-0070
Music, Comedy, Nightlife; UP Comedy Club; What's UP? UP Comedy Club is Chicago's new premier comedy club. Featuring the best in headline stand-up comedy, sketch comedy and improv revues created and presented by Second City Theatricals, UP Comedy Club is Chicago's hot new destination for comedy with shows 7 nights a week! In addition to ... ; 230 W. N. Ave., 3rd Floor Chicago, IL 60614; Chicago; (312) 662-4562
